In this American English pronunciation video, we're going to learn how to pronounce the P and B consonants.
在这段美式英语发音视频中，我们将学习如何发音P和B辅音。
These two sounds are paired together because they take the same mouth position.
这两个音被放在一起是因为它们的口型相同。
P is unvoiced, P, meaning only air passes through the mouth, and B is voiced, b, meaning you make a sound with the vocal cords, b.
P是不发声的，P，意味着只有空气通过口腔，而B是发声的，b，意味着你用声带发出声音，b。
The lips stay together while the teeth part a little.
嘴唇保持闭合，而牙齿稍微分开。
The tongue position doesn't matter for these consonants, so the tongue can start to get into position for the next sound.
对于这些辅音，舌头的位置并不重要，因此舌头可以开始为下一个音做准备。
For example, if the next sound is the R consonant, the tongue can move back and up for the R, while the lips close for the B.
例如，如果下一个音是R辅音，舌头可以向后和向上移动为R做准备，而嘴唇为B闭合。
Bring.
Let's see the sounds up close and in slow motion.
让我们近距离慢动作观察这些音。
The lips press together, and then release.
嘴唇紧闭，然后放开。
These are stop consonants.
这些是爆破音。
In stop consonants, there are two parts.
在爆破音中，有两个部分。
There's a stop of the airflow, and a release.
有一个气流的停止和一个释放。
The stop of the airflow happens as the lips close.
气流的停止发生在嘴唇闭合时。
Happen.
The release is when the lips part and the air comes through.
释放是当嘴唇分开，空气通过时。
Pn.
Happen.
Sometimes, native speakers don't release stop consonants when they come at the end of a sentence, or when the next word begins with a consonant.
有时，当爆破音在句子末尾或下一个单词以辅音开头时，母语者不会释放爆破音。
For example, the common phrase, what's up?
例如，常用短语，what's up?
My lips closed in the P position, but I didn't release the air.
我的嘴唇在P的位置闭合，但我没有释放空气。
What's up?
Another example, nap time.
另一个例子，nap time。
Nap time.
My lips came together, for the P, but they didn't release the air.
我的嘴唇为P闭合，但没有释放空气。
I stopped the air with my lips, then released it with the next sound, the T consonant.
我用嘴唇阻止了空气，然后在下一个音T辅音时释放。
Nap time.
Let's look at some words up close and in slow motion.
让我们近距离慢动作观察一些单词。
The word best.
单词best。
The lips press together, and then release into the EH as in bed vowel.
嘴唇紧闭，然后释放成EH如bed的元音。
The word rip.
单词rip。
The lips press together, and then release.
嘴唇紧闭，然后释放。
The P and B consonants.
P和B辅音。
Best.
Spot.
Rip.
Example words.
示例单词。
Repeat with me.
跟我重复。
Bring.
Baby.
Job.
Peace.
Price.
P.
Up.